MADALENA ANTUNES

JUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT



https://github.com/Madalena Antunes



https://www.linkedin.com/in/madalena-antunes-ba1509258/



912 892 058



madalena.nfantunes@gmail.com



Lisboa, Portugal

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Escola Secundária de Palmela

2019 - 2021

FORMAÇÃO DE ATORES

Evoé - Escola De Atores

2021 - 2022

ANALYTICAL PSYCOLOGY

Fátima Ponte

2022 - Present

FULLSTACK DEVELOPMENT

Bytes4Future

01/2024 - 06/2024

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS and Javascript
- · React and Next.js
- MongoDB
- Design in Figma, Canva and Illustrator
- Video editing (Sony Vegas,
 Wondershare Filmora, CapCut)
- Communication
- Conflict Resolution
- Creativity

SUMMARY

I am 20 years old and completed high school in 2021. I then started studying theater and dance while looking for a job that would allow me to continue practicing. In 2022, I took the opportunity to join a Digital Marketing Agency, where I gained valuable knowledge and experience in this field. Subsequently, I enrolled in Bytes4Future, which provided me the opportunity to deepen my knowledge and effectively enter the world of web development. I am also studying Analytical Psycology.

EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL MARKETING

Lux Digital

09/2022 - 01/2024

- Customer service / Content production
- · Training in commercial prospecting and writing
- Social media management, content production, and customer service

CLOTHING STORE

H&M

12/2023 - 01/2024

- Sales consultant
- Customer service
- Store organization

PROJECTS

Calmly

2024

Calmly is a mental health project designed to empower individuals and organizations with tools to manage their emotions effectively in daily life. Through a combination of evidence-based practices and an innovative AI companion, Calmly fosters a supportive environment for emotional processing and self-care.

Pomodoro

2024

It was a 24h challenge. We created an app for lovers of the Pomodoro Technique that incorporates statistics, tasks, and a store.